Guide to the Secretary's Office, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence and subject files, 1929-1953; Series III
  - Licences to store motion picture film, 1933-1938 (Box 222, Folder 988a)
  - Liquor: the serving of liquor at the University, 1933 (Box 222, Folder 989)
  - M, 1929-1939 (Box 222, Folder 990-995)
  - M, 1934-1941 (Box 223, Folder 996-1003)
  - M, 1941-1953 (Box 224, Folder 1004-1011)
  - Management, International Conference on, undated (Box 224, Folder 1012)
  - Manson Collection, 1938-1940 (Box 224, Folder 1013)
  - Map, 1937-1938 (Box 224, Folder 1014)
  - Marshall-Allison Fellowship, 1948-1950 (Box 224, Folder 1015)
  - Medicine, School of, 1937-1940 (Box 224, Folder 1016)
  - Medicine, School of, 1941-1953 (Box 225, Folder 1017-1019)
  - Medicine, School of: dormitory, 1952-1953 (Box 225, Folder 1020)
  - Meeks, Everett V., 1929-1942 (Box 225, Folder 1021)
  - Memorials, 1929-1950 (Box 225, Folder 1022)
  - Memorials, Committee on, 1940-1946 (Box 225, Folder 1023)
  - Memorial Service: President Hadley and Chief Justice Taft, 1930 (Box 225, Folder 1024)
  - Military Science, Department of, 1942-1948 (Box 225, Folder 1025)
  - Miller, Ogden D., 1938-1939 (Box 225, Folder 1026)
  - Morse-Draper Celebration, 1930 (Box 225, Folder 1027)
  - Mortality statistics, 1938 (Box 225, Folder 1028)
  - Mory"s Association, 1939 (Box 225, Folder 1029)
  - Murdock, George P., 1950 (Box 225, Folder 1030)
  - Music, Carnegie Grant for Undergraduates, 1939-1943 (Box 225, Folder 1031)
  - Music, School of, 1939-1953 (Box 225, Folder 1032-1033)
  - N, 1929-1953 (Box 226, Folder 1034-1043)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1951 (Box 226, Folder 1044)
  - National Recovery Act, 1933 (Box 226, Folder 1045)
  - National Student Association, 1948 (Box 227, Folder 1046)
  - Naval, Military, and Air Service Departments, Committee, 1949 (Box 227, Folder 1047)
  - Naval Science Department, 1941-1952 (Box 227, Folder 1048-1050)
  - Naval Science Laboratory, 1948 (Box 227, Folder 1051)
  - Newberry, Mrs. Thurman H., 1931 (Box 227, Folder 1052)
  - Newberry Memorial Organ, 1929 (Box 227, Folder 1053)
  - New England Colleges Association, 1952 (Box 227, Folder 1054)
  - New England Council Certificate, undated (Box 227, Folder 1054a)
  - New Haven, Chamber of Commerce, 1945-1946 (Box 227, Folder 1055)
  - New Haven, Public Improvements, 1948 (Box 227, Folder 1056)
  - New Haven Symphony, 1931 (Box 227, Folder 1057)
  - New Haven Tercentenary, 1937-1938 (Box 227, Folder 1058)
  - New Haven YMCA Junior College, 1945-1946 (Box 227, Folder 1059)
  - New Haven War Council, 1944-1946 (Box 227, Folder 1060)
  - New office, 1941 (Box 227, Folder 1061)
  - News Bureau: publicity, 1938, 1942 (Box 227, Folder 1062)
  - News Bureau, 1943-1948 (Box 228, Folder 1063-1065)
  - News Bureau, University, 1950-1953 (Box 228, Folder 1066)
  - News clippings, Yale University, January-March 1938 (Box 228, Folder 1067-1069)
  - Newton Gallery, 1934 (Box 228, Folder 1070)
  - New York World"s Fair, 1938-1940 (Box 228, Folder 1071)
  - New York Yale Club: dinner for President Seymour, 1937 (Box 228, Folder 1072)
  - Norfolk Music School, 1941-1942 (Box 228, Folder 1073)
  - Nursing, School of, 1940-1950 (Box 228, Folder 1074)
  - O, 1929-1938 (Box 228, Folder 1075-1077)
  - O, 1938-1951 (Box 229, Folder 1078-1080)
  - Occupational Medicine and Hygiene, Institute of, 1945 (Box 229, Folder 1081)
  - Old Age Assistance Tax, 1936-1937 (Box 229, Folder 1082)
  - Oviatt, Edwin, 1930 (Box 229, Folder 1083)
  - P, 1929-1935 (Box 229, Folder 1084-1087)
  - P, 1935-1946 (Box 230, Folder 1088-1096)
  - P, 1944-1952 (Box 231, Folder 1097-1100)
  - Peabody Museum, 1930-1932 (Box 231, Folder 1101)
  - Peabody Museum, 1938-1940 (Box 231, Folder 1102)
  - Pelatiah Perit Chair(s), 1934 (Box 231, Folder 1103)
  - Personnel, Advisory Committee on, 1944 (Box 231, Folder 1104)
  - Personnel Director, R. Carter Nyman, 1939-1941 (Box 231, Folder 1105)
  - Personnel Director, R. Carter Nyman, 1943-1947 (Box 231, Folder 1106)
  - Personnel register, 1944 (Box 231, Folder 1107)
  - Placement Service, Yale Alumni, 1944-1946 (Box 231, Folder 1108)
  - Portrait painters, 1938 (Box 231, Folder 1109)
  - Presidency: Voting, candidates, general, 1936-1937 (Box 231, Folder 1110)
  - Presidential survey, 1949 (Box 231, Folder 1111)
  - President"s Advisory Committee, Report of, 1952 (Box 231, Folder 1112)
  - President"s Committee on University Development, 1940 (Box 231, Folder 1113)
  - President"s Reports, 1929-1932 (Box 232, Folder 1114-1121)
  - Press clippings, 1938 (Box 232, Folder 1122)
  - Printers, Celebrations of College, 1940 (Box 232, Folder 1123)
  - Prize accounts, 1947 (Box 232, Folder 1124)
  - Prizes, 1929-1930 (Box 232, Folder 1125)
  - Prizes, 1930-1937 (Box 233, Folder 1126-1132)
  - Prizes, 1937-1945 (Box 234, Folder 1133-1139)
  - Prizes, 1943-1947 (Box 235, Folder 1140-1142)
  - Prizes A-M, 1947-1948 (Box 235, Folder 1143)
  - Prizes N-Z, 1947-1948 (Box 235, Folder 1144)
  - Prizes A-L, 1948-1949 (Box 235, Folder 1145)
  - Prizes M-W, 1948-1949 (Box 235, Folder 1146)
  - Prizes A-N, 1949-1950 (Box 235, Folder 1147)
  - Prizes P-W, 1949-1950 (Box 236, Folder 1148)
  - Prizes: preparatory school winners, 1934-1938 (Box 236, Folder 1149)
  - Prizes, Order, 1946-1950 (Box 236, Folder 1150-1153)
  - Prospective Students, 1929-1948 (Box 236, Folder 1154-1157)
  - Provost"s Office, 1943-1947 (Box 237, Folder 1158)
  - Publicity and public relations, 1931,1938-1947 (Box 237, Folder 1159)
  - Q, 1938-1948 (Box 237, Folder 1160)
  - Quadrangles, 1931 (Box 237, Folder 1161)
  - Questionnaire statistics, 1933-1945 (Box 237, Folder 1162-1169)
  - Questionnaire statistics, 1943-1953 (Box 238, Folder 1170-1175)
  - R, 1929-1935 (Box 238, Folder 1176-1181)
  - R, 1935-1944 (Box 239, Folder 1182-1190)
  - R, 1944-1950 (Box 240, Folder 1191-1193)
  - Race discrimination, 1945-1953 (Box 240, Folder 1194-1195)
  - Radio, 1939-1941 (Box 240, Folder 1196)
  - Reading lists, 1930-1933 (Box 240, Folder 1197-1199)
  - Recording of speeches, 1940 (Box 240, Folder 1200)
  - Reds, 1948-1952 (Box 240, Folder 1201)
  - Registrar"s report to Dean, 1936 (Box 240, Folder 1202)
  - Registration, 1934-1953 (Box 241, Folder 1203-1208)
  - Reports to the President, 1945-1946 (Box 241, Folder 1209)
  - Requisition forms, 1941-1946 (Box 241, Folder 1210)
  - Research: practices and policies relating to industrial and cooperative research, 1944 (Box 241, Folder 1211)
  - Reunions, 1937-1946 (Box 241, Folder 1212-1219)
  - Reunions, 1946-1952 (Box 242, Folder 1220-1221)
  - Rochester, University of, 1938-1939 (Box 242, Folder 1222)
  - Rogers, Bruce, 1948 (Box 242, Folder 1223)
  - Rollins, Carl P.: dinner, undated (Box 242, Folder 1224)
  - Rostow, Eugene: book on oil industry, 1948 (Box 242, Folder 1225)
  - Royal Asiatic Society of Bengal, 1937-1940 (Box 242, Folder 1226)
  - S, 1929-1934 (Box 242, Folder 1227-1233)
  - S, 1934-1940 (Box 243, Folder 1234-1241)
  - S, 1940-1946 (Box 244, Folder 1242-1251)
  - S, 1946-1953 (Box 245, Folder 1252-1254)
  - Saint Paul"s School, 1936 (Box 245, Folder 1255)
  - Schlesinger, Frank: memorial service, 1944 (Box 245, Folder 1256)
  - Scholarship, Committee on Enrollment and, 1943 (Box 245, Folder 1257)
  - Scholarships, 1936-1952 (Box 245, Folder 1258)
  - Secretary"s Office, letters to: eccentric, 1936-1939 (Box 245, Folder 1259-1262)
  - Secretary"s Office, letters to: eccentric, 1940-1946 (Box 246, Folder 1263-1266)
  - Selective Service, Office of, 1948-1951 (Box 246, Folder 1267)
  - Semantics, 1948-1949 (Box 246, Folder 1268)
  - Service Bureaus, Yale University, 1931-1950 (Box 246, Folder 1269-1270)
  - Seymour, Charles, 1937-1950 (Box 246, Folder 1271-1273)
  - Seymour Arms, undated (Box 247, Folder 1274)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1931-1944 (Box 247, Folder 1275)
  - Sheffield Scientific School: building, 1931-1932 (Box 247, Folder 1276-1277)
  - Sheffield Scientific School: centennial, 1946-1947 (Box 247, Folder 1278-1280)
  - Sheffield Scientific School: centennial circulars, 1946-1947 (Box 247, Folder 1281)
  - Sheffield Scientific School: centennial honorary degrees, 1946-1947 (Box 247, Folder 1282)
  - Sheffield Scientific School: invitations, 1932-1933 (Box 248, Folder 1283)
  - Sheppard, Walter B., 1933 (Box 248, Folder 1284-1285)
  - Sherman, Nathaniel, 1936-1938 (Box 248, Folder 1286)
  - Ship"s Library-Victory, 1945 (Box 248, Folder 1287)
  - Smith, David S., 1932-1939 (Box 248, Folder 1288)
  - Sons of the American Revolution, 1941 (Box 248, Folder 1289)
  - Speakers on controversial subjects at Yale, 1939 (Box 248, Folder 1290)
  - Sterling Chemistry Laboratory, 1938 (Box 248, Folder 1291)
  - Sterling Divinity Quadrangle, 1931-1932 (Box 248, Folder 1292)
  - Sterling Dormitories, 1929 (Box 248, Folder 1293)
  - Sterling Law Buildings, 1929-1935 (Box 248, Folder 1294-1295)
  - Sterling Memorial Library, 1929-1952 (Box 248, Folder 1296-1298)
  - Sterling Memorial Library: dedication, 1931 (Box 249, Folder 1299)
  - Stiles, Ezra: gravestone, 1933 (Box 249, Folder 1300)
  - Stone Letterer, 1933-1935 (Box 249, Folder 1301)
  - Street Traffic Research, Bureau for, 1939-1942 (Box 249, Folder 1302)
  - Strike by the C.I.O., 1941-1942 (Box 249, Folder 1303)
  - Student Appointment Bureau, 1950-1953 (Box 249, Folder 1304)
  - Summer Session, 1951-1952 (Box 249, Folder 1305)
  - T, 1929-1940 (Box 249, Folder 1306-1311)
  - T, 1940-1953 (Box 250, Folder 1312-1318)
  - Tax deduction, 1948 (Box 250, Folder 1319)
  - Tax exemption, 1923-1934 (Box 250, Folder 1320)
  - Ten Eyck Prize: speaking contest, 1940 (Box 250, Folder 1321)
  - Tenure, 1943 (Box 250, Folder 1322)
  - Thompson, Daniel V. of Daniel Varney, Ltd., 1945-1949 (Box 250, Folder 1323)
  - Thorpe, Malcolm R., 1937-1938 (Box 250, Folder 1324)
  - Tompkins, Ray House [with architectural plans], 1931-1933 (Box 250, Folder 1325)
  - Travel Expenses, 1930 (Box 250, Folder 1325a)
  - Treasurer"s Office, 1931-1953 (Box 251, Folder 1326-1338)
  - Tugwell, Rexford G., 1934 (Box 251, Folder 1339)
  - Tuttle, Roger W., 1937-1938 (Box 251, Folder 1340)
  - U, 1930-1953 (Box 252, Folder 1341-1344)
  - Undergraduate membership in the Yale Club, New York, 1934 (Box 252, Folder 1345)
  - Undergraduate schools: courses of study, 1940-1950 (Box 252, Folder 1346)
  - United Nations Organization: site, 1946 (Box 252, Folder 1347)
  - United States House of Representatives: questionnaire, 1944 (Box 252, Folder 1348)
  - United States of Education, 1943-1945 (Box 252, Folder 1349)
  - University Chaplain, 1931 (Box 252, Folder 1350)
  - University Council Reports, 1947-1950 (Box 252, Folder 1351-1352)
  - University development, 1949-1952 (Box 252, Folder 1353)
  - V, 1929-1938 (Box 252, Folder 1354-1356)
  - V, 1938-1953 (Box 253, Folder 1357-1360)
  - Vanderbilt, F. W. re: portrait, 1944-1946 (Box 253, Folder 1361)
  - W, 1929-1937 (Box 253, Folder 1362-1369)
  - W, 1937-1953 (Box 254, Folder 1370-1380)
  - Walker, Charles R., 1942-1944 (Box 254, Folder 1381)
  - Walker, Fred, undated (Box 254, Folder 1382)
  - Wallace, Malcolm L., 1949 (Box 254, Folder 1383)
  - Washington, George: celebration of the bicentennial of his birth, 1931-1932 (Box 254, Folder 1384)
  - Webster House, 1936 (Box 254, Folder 1385)
  - Webster"s Dictionary, 1942 (Box 254, Folder 1386)
  - Weigle, Luther A., 1938 (Box 254, Folder 1387)
  - Whitney, Eli: cotton gin, 1936-1937 (Box 254, Folder 1388)
  - Who's Who in America: advertising in, 1937-1938 (Box 255, Folder 1389)
  - Wiggin, Frederick H., 1937-1947 (Box 255, Folder 1390)
  - Wiggin, Frederick H., 1951-1953 (Box 255, Folder 1391)
  - Wilkie, Wendell, 1941 (Box 255, Folder 1392)
  - WOCD: [wired radio station system], 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1393)
  - Wolfs, Wilma, 1943 (Box 255, Folder 1394)
  - Women"s dormitory, 1932-1940 (Box 255, Folder 1395)
  - Woodbridge Hall with architectural drawing, 1927-1940 (Box 255, Folder 1396)
  - Woolsey Hall, 1937-1950 (Box 255, Folder 1397-1398)
  - World War II
    - Civil Aeronautics Authority, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1399)
    - Draftees, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1400)
    - Executive Committee, Faculty of Arts and Sciences, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1401)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1402)
    - Military training, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1403)
    - National Defense, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1404)
    - Naval Reserve Training, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1405)
    - News releases, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1406)
    - Oxford and Cambridge faculty wives, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1407)
    - Reserve officers on faculty, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1408)
    - Refugee children, 1940-1941 (Box 255, Folder 1409)
    - Selective Service, 1940-1941 (Box 256, Folder 1410)
    - University War Council, 1940-1941 (Box 256, Folder 1411)
    - War Material Collection, 1940-1941 (Box 256, Folder 1412)
    - Yale-Harvard Symposium, 1940-1941 (Box 256, Folder 1413)
    - Air Raid Wardens and precautions, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1414)
    - Army Air Corps, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1415)
    - Certificates, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1416)
    - Enemy aliens, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1417)
    - Faculty engaged in National Defense, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1418)
    - Letter to recent graduate in the service, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1419)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1420)
    - National Defense, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1421)
    - National Defense, Elliot D. Smith Committee on, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1422)
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development: blank patent forms, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1423)
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development: correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1424)
    - Press releases, pamphlets and circulars, 1941-1942 (Box 256, Folder 1425)
    - Press releases, pamphlets and circulars, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1426)
    - Safeguarding of the University"s art collections, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1427)
    - Selective Service, Committee on, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1428)
    - Student preparation for government service, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1429)
    - Supplement to University Bulletin, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1430)
    - War Department Reserve Pool, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1431)
    - War economics, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1432)
    - University Defense, Committee on: minutes, 1941-1942 (Box 257, Folder 1433)
    - Army-Navy College Training Program, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1434)
    - Bureau of Military Information Tompkins, James M., 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1435)
    - Lists, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1436)
    - Manning tables, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1437)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1438)
    - Navy, lists prepared for, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1439)
    - Office of Naval Officer Procurement, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1440)
    - Office of Scientific Research and Development, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1441)
    - Post-War Planning and Reconstruction, Committee on, 1942 (Box 257, Folder 1442)
    - Selective Service, Committee on, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1443)
    - Student Preparation for War Service, Committee on, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1444)
    - Summary of government statements to undergraduates, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1445)
    - United States Naval Reserve, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1446)
    - University Defense: air raid Procedure, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1447)
    - War economics, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1448)
    - War Manpower Commission, 1942-1943 (Box 257, Folder 1449)
    - War Training Coordinating Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 258, Folder 1450)
    - Army Air Forces Technical Training, 1942-1943 (Box 258, Folder 1451)
    - Army Specialized Training Program, 1942-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1452)
    - Married Veterans, 1946 (Box 258, Folder 1453)
    - Memorials, 1945-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1454)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1943-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1455)
    - Naval Training Unit, 1943-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1456)
    - Navy V-12 Executive Orders, 1943-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1457-1459)
    - University Defense: air raid procedure, 1943-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1460)
    - V-E Day, 1944-1945 (Box 258, Folder 1461)
    - V-J Day, 1945 (Box 258, Folder 1462)
    - War certificates, 1943-1946 (Box 258, Folder 1463)
    - War certificates
      - The Freshman Year, 1943-1946 (Box 259, Folder 1464)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1946 (Box 259, Folder 1465)
      - School of Fine Arts and School of Music, 1943-1946 (Box 259, Folder 1466)
      - Sheffield Scientific School, 1944-1946 (Box 259, Folder 1467)
      - Yale College, 1943-1946 (Box 259, Folder 1468)
      - "Yale at War", 1943-1944 (Box 259, Folder 1469)
    - Honor Rolls, 1946-1948 (Box 259, Folder 1470)
    - Yale Studies for Returning Serviceman, 1944-1948 (Box 259, Folder 1471)
    - "Yale in World War II" Kone, Eugene: Editor, 1946-1948 (Box 259, Folder 1472)
    - Dedication of War Memorial Tablets, 1950 (Box 259, Folder 1473-1474)
    - Yale in World War II, 1949-1951 (Box 259, Folder 1475)
  - Wrexham Fund, 1929-1930 (Box 259, Folder 1476)
  - X-Y-Z, 1929-1953 (Box 260, Folder 1477-1482)
  - Yale Alumni Magazine, 1937-1952 (Box 260, Folder 1483-1484)
  - Yale Alumni Music Committee, 1926-1938 (Box 260, Folder 1485)
  - Yale Alumni Weekly, 1933-1937 (Box 260, Folder 1486)
  - Yale Chair, 1941 (Box 261, Folder 1487)
  - Yale Christian Association, [undated] (Box 261, Folder 1488)
  - Yale Daily News, 1937-1945 (Box 261, Folder 1489)
  - Yale Dames, 1941 (Box 261, Folder 1490)
  - Yale Dramatic Association, 1934-1949 (Box 261, Folder 1491)
  - Yale, Elihu, 1931 (Box 261, Folder 1492)
  - Yale, Elihu: portrait, 1941 (Box 261, Folder 1493)
  - Yale, Elihu: stamp, 1949 (Box 261, Folder 1494)
  - Yale, Elihu: tercentenary, 1947-1948 (Box 261, Folder 1496)
  - Yale, gifts to, 1929-1940 (Box 261, Folder 1497-1501)
  - Yale, gifts to, 1940-1953 (Box 262, Folder 1502-1507)
  - Yale Glee Club, 1936-1940 (Box 262, Folder 1508-1510)
  - Yale Glee Club, 1940-1953 (Box 263, Folder 1511-1518)
  - Yale Glee Club Associates, 1948-1950 (Box 263, Folder 1519)
  - Yale Guide Service, 1932,1938-1940 (Box 263, Folder 1520)
  - Yale History: Pierson, George Wilson, 1941-1952 (Box 264, Folder 1521)
  - Yale, History, 1935-1939 (Box 264, Folder 1522)
  - Yale in China, 1944-1945 (Box 264, Folder 1523)
  - "Yale Interprets the News", 1944-1945 (Box 264, Folder 1524)
  - Yale Name, Seal, Arms, 1929-1939 (Box 264, Folder 1525-1529)
  - Yale Name, Seal, Arms, 1939-1953 (Box 265, Folder 1530-1533)
  - Yale and New Haven, 1930-1937 (Box 265, Folder 1534-1538)
  - Yale and New Haven, 1936-1942 (Box 266, Folder 1539-1541)
  - Yale photographs: correspondence re, 1929-1935 (Box 266, Folder 1542)
  - Yale Press, 1932-1943 (Box 266, Folder 1543-1547)
  - Yale Press, 1944-1947 (Box 267, Folder 1548-1549)
  - Yale Press [with architectural plans], 1949-1953 (Box 267, Folder 1550)
  - Yale Press: orders, 1935-1940 (Box 267, Folder 1551-1553)
  - Yale Press: Printing Office, 1938-1943, 1950-1953 (Box 267, Folder 1554-1556)
  - Yale Press: Prints, [undated] (Box 268, Folder 1557)
  - Yale Review, 1938 (Box 268, Folder 1558)
  - Yale Song Book, 1933-1935 (Box 268, Folder 1559)
  - Yale Symphony Orchestra, 1939-1941 (Box 268, Folder 1560)
  - Yale tableware, 1948 (Box 268, Folder 1561)
  - Yale University, "New" Archibald MacLeish, 1934 (Box 268, Folder 1562)
  - Yale vessels, 1952-1953 (Box 268, Folder 1563)
  - Yale visitors, 1929-1948 (Box 268, Folder 1564-1568)
  - Yale visitors, 1948-1953 (Box 269, Folder 1569-1571)
- Subject file, 1899-1953; Series IV
  - Addresses, Commemorative Exercise, Dedications and Memorials
    - Inauguration of Arthur Twining Hadley, 1899 (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Two Hundredth Anniversary of the Founding of Yale College, 1901 (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Two Hundredth Anniversary of the Birth of Jonathan Edwards, 1903 (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Centennial of the Medical School, 1914 (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Civil War Memorial Dedication, 1915 (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Two Hundredth Anniversary of the Removal of Yale to New Haven, 1916 (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Yale Pageant, 1916 (Box 270, Folder 6a)
    - Issues of the War, undated (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Dedications and Memorials, 1917-1919 (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Patriotic Celebration, 1918 (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Commemorative Exercises in Honor of the Yale Men who gave their lives in the War, 1919 (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Convocation of Cardinal Mercier, 1919 (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Dedications and Memorials, 1920-1929 (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Convocation of Marshall Foch, 1921 (Box 270, Folder 13)
    - Centennial of the Divinity School, 1922 (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - Convocation of His Royal Highness, the Crown Prince of Sweden, 1926 (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - Dedications and Memorials, 1947 (Box 270, Folder 16)
  - Addresses and Publications
    - Addresses at the Induction of President Dwight, 1886 (Box 271, Folder 17)
    - Admission requirements, [1914?] (Box 271, Folder 18)
    - Historical prints of New Haven, 1910 (Box 271, Folder 19)
    - Inauguration of Arthur Twining Hadley, 1899 (Box 271, Folder 20)
    - An Introduction to Yale, 1935, 1939, 1949 (Box 271, Folder 21)
    - Life at Yale, 1914 (Box 271, Folder 22)
    - Memorial Quadrangle, 1917, 1921 (Box 271, Folder 23)
    - The Past, Present and Future of the School of Medicine and Affiliated Institutions, 1922 (Box 271, Folder 24)
    - A Visit to Yale-in-China, 1920 (Box 271, Folder 25)
  - Alumni University Day Program, 1914-1915, 1917-1924 (Box 271, Folder 26)
  - Alumni University Day Program, 1925-1936 (Box 271, Folder 27-29)
  - Alumni University Day Program, 1937-1939, 1941-1942, 1947-1949 (Box 271, Folder 30)
  - Appointments
    - 1902-1912 (Box 272, Folder 31-41)
    - 1913-1919 (Box 273, Folder 42-48)
    - Appointment blanks, 1920 (Box 274, Folder 49)
  - Music and correspondence re: "Bright College Years"
    - Folio A-Z (Box 274, Folder 50)
    - A-B (Box 275, Folder 51)
    - C-D (Box 275, Folder 52)
    - E-G (Box 275, Folder 53)
    - H-L (Box 275, Folder 54)
    - M-O (Box 275, Folder 55)
    - P-R (Box 275, Folder 56)
    - S (Box 275, Folder 57)
    - T-V (Box 275, Folder 58)
    - W-Z (Box 275, Folder 59)
    - Form Letters and lists re: "Bright College Years", [ca.1919-1924] (Box 275, Folder 60)
  - Cabinet Meetings, 1937-1952 (Box 276, Folder 61-72)
  - Circular letters
    - Volume I (Box 277, Folder 73)
    - Volume II (Box 278, Folder 74)
  - Commencement programs
    - 1901-1902, 1903 lacking, 1904-1909 (Box 279, Folder 75)
    - 1910-1929 (Box 279, Folder 76-83)
    - 1930-1945 (Box 280, Folder 84-90)
    - 1946 lacking, 1947 (Box 280, Folder 91)
    - 1948-1949 (Box 280, Folder 92)
  - Council"s Committee on Publications
    - Abbott, Wilbur C., 1915-1924 (Box 281, Folder 93)
    - Adams, C.F., 1920 (Box 281, Folder 93)
    - Adams, Ephraim D., 1922-1923 (Box 281, Folder 93)
    - Adams, George B., 1915-1922 (Box 281, Folder 93)
    - Adams, John C., 1920 (Box 281, Folder 94)
    - Adams, Thomas S., 1920-1929 (Box 281, Folder 94)
    - Allen, T. George, 1923 (Box 281, Folder 94)
    - Allinson, Francis G., 1918-1920 (Box 281, Folder 94)
    - Allinson, John M.S., 1926-1936 (Box 281, Folder 95)
    - Anderson, Frederick, 1918 (Box 281, Folder 95)
    - Anderson, Rudolph J., 1931 (Box 281, Folder 95)
    - Andrews, Charles M., 1915-1933 (Box 281, Folder 95)
    - Angell, James R., 1923-1936 (Box 281, Folder 96)
    - Angler, Roswell P., 1915-1933 (Box 281, Folder 96)
    - Archer, John C., 1917 (Box 281, Folder 97)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton F., 1928 (Box 281, Folder 97)
    - Arnold, Thurman, 1935 (Box 281, Folder 97)